Guide to the Duke Photography Faculty and Staff Photographs, circa 1960s-2003 UA.12.03.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Faculty and Staff Photographs, 1
  - Johnson, Julie, 800
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Kristina, 801
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Johnson, Lewis, 802
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Sally, 803
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Simon, 804
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Stephanie, 805
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jokerst, Nan, 806
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jollis, James, 807
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jones, Edwin L., 808
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jones, L. Gregory, 809
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Jones, Susan P., 810
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jones, Trina, 811
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Joseph, James, 812
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Joyce, Kathleen, 813
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Joyner, Julie, 814
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Kabala, Zbigniew, 815
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Kahr, Toby, 816
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Kamakura, Wagner, 817
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Kaplan, Alice, 818
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kaplan, Leonard and Tobee, 819
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kaplan, Roger, 820
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Karsenti, Arnaud, 821
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Karson, Jeff, 822
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kasibhatla, Prasad, 823
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Kasichke, Eric, 824
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Katongole, Emmanuel, 825
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Katul, Gabriel, 826
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Katz, Andrea, 827
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Katz, David, 828
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Katz, Lawrence, 829
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kay, Helen, 830
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kay, Richard, 831
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Keck, Andy, 832
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Kedem, Gershon, 833
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Keefe, Anne, 834
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kegley, Dale, 835
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Keineg, Paol, 836
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Keith, Christopher, 837
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Keller, Thomas F., 838
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kelley, Judith, 839
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kelly, Allen, 840
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kelsoe, Garnett, 841
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kenan, Patrick, 842
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kenan, Randall, 843
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kendrick, Colleen, 844
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kennedy, Chris, 845
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Keohane, Bob, 846
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Keohane, Nan, 847
    - Photographs, folder 1 of 2 (Box 12)
    - Photographs, folder 2 of 2 (Box 12)
    - CDs (Box 25)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kerckhoff, Alan, 848
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Keyssar, Alex, 849
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kidder, Tracy, 850
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kiehart, Daniel, 851
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kimbrough, Kent, 852
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - King, Bernice A., 853
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - King, Bill, 854
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - King, Jennifer Higa, 855
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kingsbury, Benedict, 856
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kingsley, Marianne, 857
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kirkland, Rebecca, 858
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kirton, Brenda, 859
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kiser, J. J., 860
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kishnani, Priya, 861
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kiss, Elizabeth, 862
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kisslo, Joe, 863
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kistler, Laura Jean, 864
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kitchen, Dorothy, 865
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kitschelt, Herbert, 866
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Klausenmeyer, Sue, 867
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Klausner, Richard, 868
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kleberg, Sally, 869
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Klein, Jill, 870
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Klopfer, Peter, 871
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Knight, Doug, 872
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Knowles, Jarol, 873
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Koch, Walter, 874
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Kocher, Craig, 875
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Koenig, Harold, 876
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kohn, Cookie, 877
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kohorn, Bruce, 878
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kolotkin, Ronette, 879
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Kondo, Motonari, 880
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Koonz, Claudia, 881
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kornberg, Mindy, 882
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kornguth, Phyllis, 883
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Korstad, Robert, 884
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kort, Wesley, 885
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Koskinen, John, 886
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Koslofsky, Regis, 887
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kossoff, Mirinda, 888
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kramer, Randy, 889
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Kraus, William, 890
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Kremen, Irwin, 891
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Krishna, Anirudh, 892
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Krishnan, K. Ranga Rama, 893
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Krolik, Jeffrey, 894
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Kroll, David, 895
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Krueger, Anne, 896
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Krzyzewski, Mickie, 897
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Krzyzewski, Mike, 898
    - Photographs (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Ku, Hsaio-Mei, 899
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Kuczak, Tracy, 900
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Kuehn, Margarethe, 901
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Kuhn, Cynthia, 902
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Kulley, Jeff, 903
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Kuniholm, Bruce, 904
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Kunst, Richard, 905
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Kurtzberg, Joanne, 906
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Kussin, Peter, 907
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Labar, Kevin, 908
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lachman, Roslyn and Melton, 909
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Ladd, Helen, 910
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lam, Chris, 911
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - LaMantia, Anthony, 912
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Landolfo, Kevin, 913
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lane, James D., 914
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lane, Priscilla, 915
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lange, David, 916
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lange, Peter, 917
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Langford, Thomas, 918
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lariviere, Martin, 919
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - LaRocca-Pitts, Elizabeth, 920
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Larsen, Jen, 921
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Laughhunn, Dan, 922
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Laursen, Tod, 923
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lawrence, Bruce, 924
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lawrence, Deborah, 925
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lawrence, Keith, 926
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lawson, Jeffrey, 927
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Le Compagnon, Betty, 928
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lebeck, Alvin, 929
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - LeCampagnon, Betty, 930
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lee, Catherine, 931
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lee, Ti-Ying, 932
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lefkowitz, Robert, 933
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Leitzel, Jim, 934
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lekavich, Carolyn, 935
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lemon, Kay, 936
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lentricchia, Frank, 937
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lerner, Bernie, 938
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lerner, Dan, 939
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lerner, Warren, 940
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Levin, Scott, 941
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Levine, Leon, 942
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Levison, John, 943
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lewin, Arie, 944
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lewis, Martin, 945
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Li, Chuan, 946
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Li, Wei, 947
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lichtenwalner, Anna, 948
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Liddle, Roger, 949
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Liebowitz, Richard, 950
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Light, Anne, 951
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lilly, Edward, 952
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lin, Anna, 953
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lin, Haifan, 954
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lin, Nan, 955
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lincoln, C. Eric, 956
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lind, Allan, 957
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Linden, Karl, 958
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lindner, Erno, 959
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lindroth, Scott, 960
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Linne, Elwood, 961
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lipper, Steven, 962
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lipton, Ari, 963
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lipton, Connie, 964
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Lischer, Richard, 965
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lisker, Donna, 966
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Littman, Michael, 967
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Litzinger, Ralph, 968
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Liu, Jie, 969
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Livingstone, Bertha, 970
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lo, Joseph, 971
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lo, Y. C., 972
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lobach, Mary, 973
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Lober, Doug, 974
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Locke, Elizabeth, 975
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Locus, Liz, 976
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Loftin, Roscoe, 977
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Loftstrom, Irene, 978
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Long, Steven, 979
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Longrie, Ann, 980
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Looney, Jackie, 981
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Love, Randall, 982
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lowe, James, 983
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Loy, Judy, 984
    - Negatives (Box 34)
  - Loyd, Roger, 985
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lozier, Susan, 986
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lucic, Richard, 987
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Luken, Ellen, 988
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Luney, Percy, 989
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lyerly, Kim, 990
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Lyles, Ken, 991
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Lynch, John, 992
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - MacFall, James, 993
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - MacIntyre, Neil, 994
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Maddox, George, 995
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Madey, John, 996
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Magat, Wesley, 997
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Maguire, Lynn, 998
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Maher, Jennifer, 999
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Maheshwary, A. C., 1000
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Malin, Peter, 1001
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Malouf, Melissa, 1002
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Mangun, George (Ron), 1003
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Mann, Joseph, 1004
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Manton, Kenneth, 1005
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - March, John, 1006
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - March, Reggie, 1007
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Marchuk, Douglas, 1008
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Marcus, Joel, 1009
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Mario, Ernie, 1010
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Markert, Louise, 1011
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Markman, Sidney, 1012
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Marks, Larry, 1013
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Marsh, Gail R., 1014
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Marshall, Roger, 1015
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Martin, Jonathan, 1016
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Martin, Judith, 1017
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Martin, Tim, 1018
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Martinez, Linda, 1019
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Massoud, Hisham, 1020
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Matchar, David, 1021
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Matthew, William, 1022
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Mauskopf, Seymour, 1023
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Maxwell, Beth, 1024
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Maxwell, Richard, 1025
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Mayer, Frederick, 1026
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Mazumdar, Sucheta, 1027
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - McAbee, Linda, 1028
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - McAllaster, Carolyn, 1029
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - McAuliffe, Jody, 1030
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - McBride, Colleen, 1031
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McCann, John, 1032
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McCarthy, Connie, 1033
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McCarthy, Gregory, 1034
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McClain, David, 1035
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McClay, Dave, 1036
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McClendon, George, 1037
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McCollough, Tom, 1038
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McCormick, Alexandra, 1039
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McCoy, Beverly, 1040
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McCraw, Beverly, 1041
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McDonald, Eugene, 1042
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McDonald, Marie, 1043
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McDonnell, Donald, 1044
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McElhaney, James H., 1045
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McElroy, Marjorie, 1046
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McElroy, Michael, 1047
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McElveen, Gregory, 1048
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McFadden, D. J., 1049
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McGee, Kris, 1050
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McGovern, Francis, 1051
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McGovern, John (Jack), 1052
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McGown, Linda, 1053
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McGrath, Kevin, 1054
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McHeyzer-Williams, Michael, 1055
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McIsaac, Peter, 1056
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McKinney, Ross, 1057
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McKinnis, Gail, 1058
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McLoyd, Vonnie, 1059
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McMahon, Alex, 1060
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - McMallan, Barbara, 1061
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McMillan, Becky, 1062
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McNamara, James, 1063
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McNeil, Diana, 1064
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McNeilly, Maya, 1065
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McNutt, Sandy, 1066
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - McWilliams, Neil, 1067
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Meador, Keith, 1068
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Meadow, Pat, 1069
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Meck, Warren, 1070
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Medearis, Ellen, 1071
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Meek, Beverly, 1072
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Megonigol, J. Patrick, 1073
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Meintjes, Louise, 1074
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Melchionni, Gary, 1075
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Meredith, Dennis, 1076
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Meredith, Jill, 1077
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Merritt, Kathy, 1078
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Metzger, Sean, 1079
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Metzloff, Tom, 1080
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Meyers, Carol, 1081
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Meyers, Eric, 1082
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Meyers, Rod, 1083
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Mezzatesta, Michael, 1084
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Michener, Lloyd, 1085
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Mickiewicz, Ellen, 1086
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Mignolo, Walter, 1087
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Milano, Carmelo, 1088
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Miller, David, 1089
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Miller, Marty, 1090
    - Negatives (Box 35)
  - Miller-Hooks, Elise, 1091
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Mills, Anita, 1092
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Minnear, Wilma, 1093
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Minnick, C. P., 1094
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Miranda, Marie Lynn, 1095
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Mirovitskaya, Natalia, 1096
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Mitchell, Will, 1097
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Mixon, Jill, 1098
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Modrich, Paul, 1099
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Moi, Toril, 1100
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Moneta, Larry, 1101
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Money, Jeff, 1102
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Monnig, Ruth, 1103
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Moon, Michael, 1104
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Mooney, Richard, 1105
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Moore, Joe, 1106
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Moore, Lawrence, 1107
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Moore, Nicholas, 1108
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Moorman, T., 1109
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Morris, Edward, 1110
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Morris, Edwin, 1111
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Morris, James J., 1112
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Morris, Madeline, 1113
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Morrison, David, 1114
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Mortensen, Carla, 1115
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Moser, Tammy, 1116
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Moses, Michael, 1117
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Mosley, Albert, 1118
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Mosteller, Bob, 1119
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Motten, Alex, 1120
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Moulin, Herve, 1121
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Mueller, Berndt, 1122
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Muir, Holly, 1123
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Munger, Michael, 1124
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Muoio, Deborah, 1125
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Murphy, Robert, 1126
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Musser, Robert, 1127
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Muti, Lorenzo, 1128
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Myers, George, 1129
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nadeau, Joseph, 1130
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Naillon, Royce, 1131
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nanco, Susan, 1132
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nardini, Maria, 1133
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nathans, Sid, 1134
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nayduch, Donna, 1135
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Neal, Mark Anthony, 1136
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Neal, Pat, 1137
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nechyba, Thomas, 1138
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Needham, Amy, 1139
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Needham, David, 1140
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Neeton, Ginny, 1141
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Neill, Daniel, 1142
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nelson, Dana, 1143
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nelson, Ken, 1144
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Neuschel, Kristen, 1145
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Nevidjon, Brenda, 1146
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Nevins, Joseph, 1147
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Newby, Kristin, 1148
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Newcity, Michael, 1149
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Newman, Mark, 1150
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Newman, Warren, 1151
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Newman, Wes, 1152
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nicholas, Peter and Virginia, 1153
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Nicolelis, Miguel, 1154
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Nightingale, Kathy, 1155
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Nijhout, Fred, 1156
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Niklason, Laura, 1157
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Niou, Emerson, 1158
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nixon, Nan, 1159
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Nolte, Loren, 1160
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Nordan, Charles, 1161
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Norris, John, 1162
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Nowicki, Stephen, 1163
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Nunez-Wolff, Charlotte, 1164
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Oakley, Sarah, 1165
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Oas, Terrence, 1166
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Oates, John, 1167
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - O'Barr, Jean, 1168
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Ocko, Johathan, 1169
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - O'Connor, Chris, 1170
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Oddone, Eugene, 1171
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Odom, Guy, 1172
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Oehler, Jerri, 1173
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Oeppen, Jim, 1174
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Ogburn, Sandy, 1175
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Oh, Seog, 1176
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - O'Halloran, Theresa, 1177
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Oliver, Lois Pound, 1178
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Oliver, Tom, 1179
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Olson, Ron, 1180
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Onken, Jane, 1181
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Opara, Emmanuel, 1182
    - Negatives (Box 36)
      Scope and Contents note
      Includes images with Brad Collins
  - Oren, Ram, 1183
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Orr, Marion, 1184
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Oster, Jerry, 1185
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Outmette, Ruth, 1186
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Overbeck, Carla, 1187
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Overhauser, David, 1188
    - Negatives (Box 36)
  - Owen, Derek, 1189
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Owen, Harry, 1190
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Owen, Rick, 1191
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Owens, Greg, 1192
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Paat, John, 1193
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Page, Bernadette, 1194
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Page, Ellis, 1195
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Page, Sharon, 1196
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Pair, Kimberly, 1197
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Paletz, David, 1198
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Palker, Thomas, 1199
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Palmer, Michael J., 1200
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Palmer, Richard, 1201
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Palmore, Erdman, 1202
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Parker, Bernice, 1203
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Parker, Maurice, 1204
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Parker, Roy, 1205
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Parkins, Robert, 1206
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Parr, Ronald, 1207
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Paschall, Karen, 1208
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Patkar, Ashwin, 1209
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Patterson, David, 1210
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Payne, Bruce, 1211
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Payne, Charles, 1212
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Payne, John, 1213
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Payne, Richard, 1214
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Peck, Gunther, 1215
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Pefley, Rich, 1216
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Peirce, Jeffrey, 1217
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Pell, Charles (Chuck), 1218
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Pell, Chuck (Charles), 1219
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pellizzari, Vickie, 1220
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Pelphrey, Kevin, 1221
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Pendergast, Ann M., 1222
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Penning, Donald, 1223
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Penry, Lorraine, 1224
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Peretto, Pietro, 1225
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Pericak-Vance, Margaret, 1226
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Perry, Gloria, 1227
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Peshkin, Catherine, 1228
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Peter, Mary Ann, 1229
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Peter, Robert, 1230
    - Negatives (Box 37)